A Guide to the Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 2 FA1440
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Financial records, 1953-1980; 14; 28.45 Cubic Feet 25 containers
  - Cash Receipts - Cash Disbursements, 1962-1963 June (Box 279)
  - Cash Receipts - Cash Disbursements, 1960 June-1961 December (Box 279)
  - Cash Receipts - Cash Disbursements, 1959-1960 May (Box 279)
  - Cash Receipts - Cash Disbursements, 1957 October-1958 (Box 279)
  - Cash Receipts - Cash Disbursements, 1953 December-1957 September (Box 279)
  - Payroll Employee Earning Cards, 1955-1965 (Box 280)
  - Payroll Journals, 1964-1968 (Box 280)
  - Hawaiian State Income Tax, 1968; 1969 (Box 280)
  - New York State Income Tax, 1959-1968 (Box 280)
  - RG Travel, 1974 (Box 280)
  - Annual Audit Reports and Financial Work Papers, 1962-1966 (Box 281)
  - Annual Audit Reports and Financial Work Papers, 1967-1968 (Box 282)
  - Annual Audit Reports and Financial Work Papers, 1969-1970 (Box 283)
  - General Ledger Accounting Book, 1971-1976 (Box 284)
  - Cash Disbursements, 1969-1978 (Box 285)